<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../helpproject.xsl" ?>
<topic template="Default" lasteditedby="Andre" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../helpproject.xsd">
  <title translate="true">Copyright</title>
  <body>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:11pt; font-style:italic;" translate="true">Realworld Software Products</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Heading1"><var styleclass="Heading1">&lt;%PRODUCTNAME%&gt;</var></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-style:italic;" translate="true">Copyright Information</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true">© </text><var styleclass="Normal">&lt;%HOLDING%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true">. All rights reserved. </text><var styleclass="Normal" style="font-style:italic;">&lt;%PRODUCTNAME%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true"> is a product manufactured by Realworld Software Products BV. </text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">The information contained in this publication is the exclusive property of </text><var styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;">&lt;%HOLDING%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">, except as otherwise indicated. You may view, copy and print documents and graphics incorporated in this publication (the “Documents”) subject to the following: (1) the Documents may be used solely for managing the described product; (2) the Documents may not be modified or altered in any way; and (3) </text><var styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;">&lt;%HOLDING%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true"> withholds permission for making the Documents or any portion thereof accessible via the Internet. Except as expressly provided herein, you may not use, copy, print, display, reproduce, publish, licence, post, transmit or distribute the Documents in whole or in part without the prior written permission of </text><var styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;">&lt;%HOLDING%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">.</text><br/><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">The information contained in this publication is subject to change without notice.</text><br/><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">The software described in this publication is supplied under licence and may be used or copied only in accordance with the terms of such licence.</text><br/><br/><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-style:italic;" translate="true">Trademarks</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><var styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;">&lt;%PRODUCTNAME%&gt;</var><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true"> is a trade mark of Realworld Software Products BV. Smallworld is a trade mark of General Electric Company. MySQL, Oracle, Oracle Express are trademarks of Oracle Corporation. Java is a trade mark of Sun Microsystems, Inc. Windows is a trade mark of Microsoft Corporation. Splunk is a registered trade mark of Splunk Inc. Linux is a trade mark of Linus Torvalds. Apache, Apache Commons, Apache Log4J are trademarks of the Apache Software Foundation. Jandex, JBoss and Hibernate are trademarks of Red Hat, Inc. DOM4J is a trade mark of MetaStuff, Ltd.</text><br/><text styleclass="Normal" style="font-size:8pt;" translate="true">Other company or product names mentioned in this documentation may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective companies.</text></para>
  </body>
</topic>
